91mobiles.com 2012-10-15

# 91Mobiles

At 91mobiles, we respect the privacy of our users and the importance of the information they entrust to us. 

**Nature of information collected**  

We may collect information that can identify you ("personal information"), such as your name and email address, your preferences, your phone numbers, in case you happen to be owner of a brand or business when you (or other users) provide it to us when using our website or in some other manner. 

We also may collect other types of information in the following ways when you visit our website: 1\. Our server logs automatically collect information, such as your IP address, your browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us track users' movements around our site and understand trends.   
2\. We may assign your computer one or more cookies which may collect information to facilitate access to our website and to personalize your online experience.   
3\. We may allow third-party advertising companies or ad networks to display advertisements on our websites.   
4\. We do not provide any personal information to these companies.   
5\. These companies may use tracking tools, such as cookies, to collect information about computers used to view or interact with their advertisements, some of which could be a part of the main result.   
6\. If you post information about yourself or others, or communicate with others using our website, please note that we cannot control who reads your postings or what they do with the information you provide. We encourage you to use caution in posting personal information.   

**Usage of such information**  

We may use information to: * Fulfill your requests for products and services, or those made in the “My” page;   
* Offer products and services that may be of interest to you;   
* Facilitate use of our website;   
* Manage your account and your preferences;   
* Analyze use of and improve our website, products and services;   
* Identify and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of our website; and   
* Enforce our Terms of Use.   

**Do we share information?**

We will not share your personal information with others except as indicated below, or except when we inform you in advance and give you the opportunity to opt out. We may share personal information with service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf; We may share aggregated, non-personal information mainly relating to aggregated statistics with advertisers and others. 

**Security** We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy** We may occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this summary, our Privacy Policy or our information practices, please email our legal experts at legal@91mobiles.com

## 

  * [ Blackberry Bold 3 9780](http://www.91mobiles.com/blackberry-bold-3-9780-price-in-india#pricepart) @ **Rs. 15,373/-**
  * [ Sony Xperia miro](http://www.91mobiles.com/sony-xperia-miro-price-in-india#pricepart) @ **Rs. 12,490/-**
  * [ Karbonn A7 Plus](http://www.91mobiles.com/karbonn-a7-plus-price-in-india#pricepart) @ **Rs. 6,239/-**
  * [ Sony Xperia miro](http://www.91mobiles.com/sony-xperia-miro-price-in-india#pricepart) @ **Rs. 12,490/-**
  * [ Zync Z909 Plus](http://www.91mobiles.com/zync-z909-plus-price-in-india#pricepart) @ **Rs. 2,849/-**
  * [ Karbonn A21 Android](http://www.91mobiles.com/karbonn-a21-android-price-in-india#pricepart) @ **Rs. 10,079/-**
  * [ Samsung Galaxy Note II N7100](http://www.91mobiles.com/samsung-galaxy-note-ii-n7100-price-in-india#pricepart) @ **Rs. 37,249/-**
  * [ HTC Mobiles Wildfire S](http://www.91mobiles.com/htc-wildfire-s-price-in-india#pricepart) @ **Rs. 8,990/-**
  * [ Micromax M2](http://www.91mobiles.com/micromax-m2-price-in-india#pricepart) @ **Rs. 1,505/-**
  * [ Micromax A57 Ninja 3](http://www.91mobiles.com/micromax-a57-ninja-3-price-in-india#pricepart) @ **Rs. 4,512/-**

**Register for Exclusive**  
Deals & Discounts

  * ### 

 [Sanni Olatunji](http://www.91mobiles.com/reviews/Tecno/T8/jjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjj/24949.html#jsid-1340346270-377) -daily use of cell phone batteries take part of the battery life,music,Radio,suffing the wed, shorting the battery life try to get a new batterry from tecno & continue to enjoy your T8

  * ### 

 [Bhaskar](http://www.91mobiles.com/reviews/Karbonn/A1/wrong+information+provided/24774.html#jsid-1340281599-699) -Is this dual sim mobile?? 

  * ### 

  * ### 

 [nishant](http://www.91mobiles.com/blog/11960/91Mobiles+Knockout++Samsung+Galaxy+Pocket+vs++Spice+MI280+vs++Micromax+A50.html#jsid-1340216630-140) -Micromax a50 is better than both of the others. 

  * ### 

 [pawankumar](http://www.91mobiles.com/reviews/Celkon/A1/All+Celkon+Mobiles/25933.html#jsid-1340187614-349) -IS THIS MOBILE GOOD OR BAD FOR INTERNET  

  * ### 

 [John Williams](http://www.91mobiles.com/blog/12725/Envent+Brings+in+Samsung+Battery+Boost+Case+to+Enhance+handset+s+battery+life+by+two+folds.html#jsid-1340186119-654) -You guys should review Mugen Power batteries for Samsung. I heard they have 5400mah battery for Galaxy Note. Can you do a review? I requested one from them for my blog. Maybe you can do the same here http://mugen.tv/2012/04/request-a-mugen-power-battery-to-review-on-your-site-blog-or-forum/

  * ### 

 [basit](http://www.91mobiles.com/blog/12350/Has+India+got+Windows+Phone+Tango+Refresh+roll+out.html#jsid-1340176977-913) -Not yet..  
I m waiting for this tango update

  * ### 

 [thakur](http://www.91mobiles.com/blog/9473/India+s+Ultra+low+Cost+Aakash+Tablet+is+on+Sale++++.html#jsid-1340129485-258) -Fuck Aakash company,,how many time i have done booking for your product Ubislate...For priority delivery i have also sent you cheque on Feb 2012, but still(on 19 June 2012) you can't inform me whether you received it or not...FUCK FUCK Aakash..

  * ### 

 [Prakash Panda](http://www.91mobiles.com/blog/11763/MTS+India+introduces+two+new+Mblaze+broadband+plans+in+Karnataka+and+Tamil+Nadu.html#jsid-1340101556-187) -MTS Broadband provides High Speed Wireless Broadband Internet in India. There are different attractive Tariff Plans available in both Prepaid as well as Postpaid payment modes. For the other regions it will be available soon.

  * ### 

 [Guest](http://www.91mobiles.com/blog/13613/VLC+media+players+app+officially+coming+to+Android.html#jsid-1340101194-910) -mBillionth International Mobile Award 2012: An Ecosystem for Mobilepreneurs

â€śThe mBillionth Award is a great platform to demonstrate the power of mobile and recognize the talents of those who are able to deploy ICT in innovative ways to help build the digital divide and create new opportunities for Indian society at large"

Register: http://goo.gl/0j0X5

  * ### 

  * ### 

 [Guest](http://www.91mobiles.com/blog/11383/Nokia+Lumia+610+to+be+available+in+India+by+mid+May.html#jsid-1339948202-152) -Which is the best windows smartphone 11000

  * ### 

 [Nadeem](http://www.91mobiles.com/blog/13410/Reliance+Communications+Introduces+Master+Plan+For+Its+Karnataka+based+GSM+Subscribers+.html#jsid-1339866459-726) -PLEASE DON'T GO FOR IT.

  * ### 

 [Nadeem](http://www.91mobiles.com/blog/13410/Reliance+Communications+Introduces+Master+Plan+For+Its+Karnataka+based+GSM+Subscribers+.html#jsid-1339866368-52) -It was supposed to be 500MB free data/month for 6 months but they are deducting it from your main balance.  
Very bad Reliance.  
Moreover, rather than apologizing for their mistake, their customer care will rudely ask you to call them back the next day to waste another 20-30 mins over the phone waiting for them to answer which is again the paid call.

  * ### 

 [Nadeem](http://www.91mobiles.com/blog/13410/Reliance+Communications+Introduces+Master+Plan+For+Its+Karnataka+based+GSM+Subscribers+.html#jsid-1339866100-368) -Dear Friends,  
Please don't go for this luring offer as Reliance is simply cheating people.  
Today I recharged my phone with Rs.74.  
After using 1 MB data the GPRS stopped working giving me the message that my account balance is zero.  
Luckily, my account balance was only Rs.10 which was deducted to access 1MB 2G data.  
I then called the customer care. They answered after 20 mins of wait time after 6 attempts just to tell that the info has not been updated in their records & they advised me to call back tomorrow again.  
I never expected such poor & pathetic service from Reliance :(  
I might soon change my operator, thanks to number portability.  
For any queries contact me at nad_pz1@yahoo.co.in
